<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-15"?>
<datos>
  <menu>
    <home>Home</home>
    <chisiamo>About Us</chisiamo>
    <servizi>Services</servizi>
    <links>Links</links>
    <contatti>Contact</contatti>
  </menu>
  <body>
    <chisi>About Us</chisi>
    <serv>Services</serv>
    <leggi>Read more</leggi>
    <consulenza>CONSULTING</consulenza>
    <cons>Consulting</cons>
    <cons1>Corporate consulting</cons1>
    <consdesc1>The study provides the necessary corporate advice and appropriate assistance in the establishment of new companies, in the revision of the...</consdesc1>
    <consdesc1a>The study provides the necessary corporate advice and appropriate assistance in the establishment of new companies, in the review of social and statutory clauses agreements, drafting of the financial statements and any explanatory notes and the interim financial statements, the preparation of all types of contracts, mergers, demergers, transformation, contribution and other extraordinary transactions, in the negotiations between members and between different societies, in performing due diligence for the acquisition of companies or businesses, in the creation or revision of shareholder agreements in liquidation and the dissolution of a company, in the establishment and management of trusts and trust, the establishment of holding companies and corporate groups in insolvency and bankruptcy proceedings in general.</consdesc1a>
    <cons2>Tax consulting</cons2>
    <consdesc2>This area contains a series of activities among which we can mention the advice in tax planning in relation to direct taxes...</consdesc2>
    <consdesc2a>This area contains a series of activities among which we can mention the advice in tax planning in the field of direct and indirect taxes, in the preparation of tax returns (mod. Unico, IRAP declaration and Sector Studies), in investigating and in controls by the tax authorities and more generally in tax litigation, the tax amnesty and various forms of amnesty, in information on tax news, analyzing the differences in taxation between the country of origin and foreign countries, the analysis international conventions.</consdesc2a>
    <cons3>Company financial consulting</cons3>
    <consdesc3>This area may include a series of activities including but not limited to refer...</consdesc3>
    <consdesc3a>This area may include a series of activities including but not limited to recalling the assistance in obtaining credit and loans by lenders and by leasing companies, in the examination of alternative financing instruments, the elaboration of financial plans and plans for sustainability of investments in corporate financial management routine (with cash flow instruments, cash flow management, etc ...), in managing relationships with lenders and obtaining cost reductions commissions and financial charges, in the planning of the financial strategy.</consdesc3a>
    <cons4>Auditing, legal and accounting advice</cons4>
    <consdesc4>This area includes the accounting and auditing activities typical of the supervisory board or organ of...</consdesc4>
    <consdesc4a>This area includes the typical accounting and legal auditing of the supervisory board or auditing and control body, the former supervisory activities. D.L. 231/2001, opinions on the correctness of the accounts on the system and the advice of an accounting system (identification of the appropriate software, creating chart of accounts and setting of accounting procedures).</consdesc4a>
    <organiz>The organization of our accounting firm</organiz>
    <organiz1>The study Accountant Dr. Pierpaolo Sanna has the goal to offer customers all the benefits within the typical business of accountants that is:</organiz1>
    <organiz2>budgets, business law, auditing and accounting certification, tax law, management of corporate crises, bankruptcy law, business backgrounds disciplines, private law.</organiz2>
    <organiz3>We offer a variety of additional services, such as the</organiz3>
    <organiz4>bookkeeping, processing pay slips, the system of cost accounting, financial analysis, preparation of budgets and business plans</organiz4>
    <organiz5>The accounting firm is organized with information and multimedia technologies both for keeping the accounts and for the processing of each practice as well as for database searches on the Internet; the firm offers to its clients a reserved area and through this the user can see their own protected space Cicolari and documents in maximum security and confidentiality of information.</organiz5>
    <ofert>Offered services</ofert>
    <ofert1>- Support the constitution and in the revision of the social regulations.</ofert1>
    <ofert2>- Assistance for corporate contracts.</ofert2>
    <ofert3>- Assistance to company negotiations.</ofert3>
    <ofert4>- Execution extraordinary transactions (mergers, demergers, transformations, transfers).</ofert4>
    <ofert5>- Consulting in the shareholders' agreements.</ofert5>
    <ofert6>- Assistance in the liquidation and corporate dissolution.</ofert6>
    <ofert7>- Consulting in the establishment of trusts and trustees.</ofert7>
    <ofert8>- Consultancy in the creation of holding companies and corporate groups.</ofert8>
    <ofert9>- Assistance to the tax returns and the field studies.</ofert9>
    <ofert10>- Support and information for the news in direct and indirect taxes.</ofert10>
    <ofert11>- Assistance in tax disputes.</ofert11>
    <ofert12>- Consulting for amnesties and pardons.</ofert12>
    <ofert13>- Analysis of differences in taxation between home and foreign countries.</ofert13>
    <ofert14>- Analysis of international conventions.</ofert14>
    <ofert15>- Consulting in obtaining credit and loans by lenders.</ofert15>
    <ofert16>- Examination of alternative financing instruments on the market.</ofert16>
    <ofert17>- Development of financial plans and sustainability of investments.</ofert17>
    <ofert18>- Planning the financial strategy, diagnosis and control of the company's financial structure.</ofert18>
    <ofert19>- Financing projects.</ofert19>
    <ofert20>- Analysis and review of financial statements.</ofert20>
    <ofert21>- Review of accounts and procedures.</ofert21>
    <ofert22>- The role of auditors and auditors.</ofert22>
    <ofert23>- Appointment of former supervisory D.L. 231/2001.</ofert23>
    <ofert24>- Preparation of financial statements.</ofert24>
    <ofert25>- Drafting notes.</ofert25>
    <title1>Accounting</title1>
    <title2>Budget analysis and management control</title2>
    <title3>Finance area and grants</title3>
    <title4>Services inherent in the Governmental agencies</title4>
    <title5>Tax services</title5>
    <title6>Other services</title6>
    <title7>Reserved area</title7>
    <cont1>This space includes a series of activities including the keeping of simplified accounting, routine bookkeeping, the management of the book of depreciable assets, assistance to the keeping of accounts by the company's</cont1>
    <cont2>including suggestions about management accounting programs.</cont2>
    <analisi1>This space includes: predictive analysis and budgeting, performance monitoring with interim budget situations, deviations analysis</analisi1>
    <analisi2>reclassifications and budget analysis with indexes, rating corporate credit rating (according to Basel 2).</analisi2>
    <area1>The firm handles to exhibit and educate funding practices and grant concessions to companies already in business that the new constitution
</area1>
    <area2>The non-repayable loans are direct loans to particular types of people (youth, women, the unemployed ...) who plan to start a business activity that falls within a specific category. Such facilities once acquired are not returned to the region that has provided them, from which developed the term "grant". The firm, in addition deals with educating these practices beyond those financing at preferential rates for certain categories of companies.</area2>
    <serv1>This space includes: support for the launch of new commercial, industrial, craft and professional</serv1>
    <serv2>(At stop shops), administrative procedures, authorizations, licenses and permits, registration documents and certifications chamber, the practical management at Tax Office, Chamber of Commerce, Office INPS, Inail Office, Office of Labor.</serv2>
    <fisca1>This space includes a series of activities including but not limited to are cited: the processing declarations</fisca1>
    <fisca2>tax 730, Unique individuals, Unique partnership, corporation Unico, IRAP, the annual tax data communications, the annual tax declaration, customer lists suppliers, blacklist lists, intra-Community transactions lists, processing 770, statement IMU, electronic transmission F24.</fisca2>
    <altri>This area includes such domiciliation of corporations and non-commercial entities.</altri>
    <riser1>Access restricted to customers with username and password; through this protected space the user can see their own data and documents in the maximum security and confidentiality of information</riser1>
    <riser2>To enable you to service and request the password</riser2>
    <riser3>click here.</riser3>
    <enti>Entities and Institutions</enti>
    <justi>Ministry of Justice</justi>
    <econ>Ministry of Economy and Finances</econ>
    <lavo>Ministry of Labour</lavo>
    <prod>Ministry of Productive Activities</prod>
    <comm>Italian Chambers of Commerce</comm>
    <cvco>Chamber of Commerce of the VCO</cvco>
    <cagli>City of Cagliari</cagli>
    <prov>Province of Cagliari</prov>
    <regi>Sardinia region</regi>
    <entra>Revenue Agency</entra>
    <banc>Bank of Italy</banc>
    <nazi>National CCIAA</nazi>
    <ordi>Professional associations</ordi>
    <dott>National Council of Certified Public Accountants</dott>
    <ordi>Order of Chartered Accountants of Cagliari</ordi>
    <union>Union Giovani Professional Accountants</union>
    <consi>National Council of Labour Consultants</consi>
    <nota>National Council of Notaries</nota>
    <degli>National Lawyers Council</degli>
    <affa>Affari Square</affa>
    <parl>Parliament</parl>
    <parla>Italian Parliament</parla>
    <depu>Chamber of Deputies</depu>
    <sena>Senate</sena>
    <borse>International scholarships</borse>
    <infom>Information</infom>
    <sole>The sun 24 hours</sole>
    <oggi>Italy Today</oggi>
    <fisco>The Revenue</fisco>
    <finaz>Finance and Revenue</finaz>
    <gazz>The Official Journal</gazz>
    <stamp>The Print</stamp>
    <corr>The Courier of the Night</corr>
    <repu>The Republic</repu>
    <sname>Name</sname>
    <slastname>Lastname</slastname>
    <smessage>Message</smessage>
    <ssend>Send</ssend>
  </body>
  <footer>
    <mcontact>Contact</mcontact>
    <address>Address</address>
  </footer>
</datos>